let questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which artist is known for coining the term 'Surrealism'?",
    options: [
      "Pablo Picasso",
      "Salvador Dali",
      "Vincent van Gogh",
      "Henri Matisse",
    ],
    answer: "Salvador Dali",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "Which movement is associated with the use of abstract forms and shapes in art?",
    options: ["Impressionism", "Expressionism", "Futurism", "Cubism"],
    answer: "Cubism",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Which artist is known for painting the work 'The Persistence of Memory'?",
    options: [
      "Pablo Picasso",
      "Salvador Dali",
      "Vincent van Gogh",
      "Henri Matisse",
    ],
    answer: "Salvador Dali",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'The Scream'?",
    options: [
      "Vincent van Gogh",
      "Salvador Dali",
      "Edvard Munch",
      "Claude Monet",
    ],
    answer: "Edvard Munch",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "What movement was associated with the use of bold, bright colors and thick brushstrokes?",
    options: ["Impressionism", "Expressionism", "Fauvism", "Cubism"],
    answer: "Fauvism",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "What movement was associated with the use of bright colors, simplified forms, and a focus on movement and speed",
    options: [
      "Impressionism",
      "Futurism",
      "Surrealism",
      "Abstract Expressionism",
    ],
    answer: "Futurism",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Water Lilies'?",
    options: ["Claude Monet", "Paul Cezanne", "Paul Gauguin", "Paul Klee"],
    answer: "Claude Monet",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Les Demoiselles d'Avignon'?",
    options: [
      "Henri Matisse",
      "Vincent van Gogh",
      "Salvador Dali",
      "Pablo Picasso",
    ],
    answer: "Pablo Picasso",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which artist is known for creating the painting 'Guernica'?",
    options: [
      "Claude Mone",
      "Paul Cezanne",
      "Pablo Picasso",
      "Vincent van Gogh",
    ],
    answer: "Pablo Picasso",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Which artist is known for creating the sculpture 'The Thinker'?",
    options: ["Auguste Rodin", "Alexander Calder", "Jean Arp", "Henry Moore"],
    answer: "Auguste Rodin",
    category: "modern-art",
  },
];
